http://www.joanallen.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Privacy and Cookie Policy
Please replace this text with you Privacy Policy.
Please add any additional cookies your website uses below (e.g. Google Analytics).
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that
you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure
that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this
request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Loading...
Menu
Sign in to your account
Metal Detectors Metal DetectorsMinelab CTX 3030Minelab Go-Find SeriesDeep Searching Metal detectorsGold Metal DetectorsUnderwater Metal DetectorsCoin & Relic Metal DetectorsSecurity Metal DetectorsIndustrial Metal DetectorsChildren's Metal DetectorsMinelab EquinoxMinelab VanquishHobby Metal DetectorsFisher Metal DetectorsMinelab Metal DetectorsQuest Metal DetectorsNokta Makro Metal DetectorsWhites Metal DetectorsViking Metal Detectors
Minelab CTX 3030
Quest Q30Brands BrandsFisherMinelabQuestJoan AllenWhitesBounty HunterLaserVikingCoiltekNokta/MakroDetector Pro Detector ProGray GhostJolly RogerNugget BusterKarmaOlight
Accessories AccessoriesEquinox AccessoriesBagsFinds PouchesBatteries & ChargersBox CoversAccessory PacksCleaning ProductsClothingGold Panning KitsDigging ToolsPinpoint ProbesHarnessesHeadphonesShaftsSparesMinelab Lifestyle RangeMinelab AccessoriesQuest AccessoriesMinelab Vanquish AccessoriesFisher Accessories
Minelab Accessories
Clothing
Pinpoint Probes
Headphones
Digging Tools
Quest Accessories
Coils CoilsCoil/Coil Cover Brands Coil/Coil Cover BrandsFisherDetechLaserMinelab MinelabGPX CoilsX-Terra CoilsE-Trac/Exp/Safari CoilsSovereign CoilsCoiltekKarmaQuest CoilsCoil coversMonoBooks & DVD'S Books & DVD'SInstruction ManualsDVD'sFindsDetectingMagazinesAndy SabischJohn LynnBrett HammondJennifer LaingPaul MurawskiRoss WhiteheadGordon BaileyNigel MillsDavid VillanuevaBarry MarsdenRainier Pudhill & Clive EyreIvan BuckLloyd LaingEdward FletcherAndrew Appels & Stuart LaycockJames DyerDennis G BlairDavid E JohnstonMartin CookDavid J BreezePeter DuckersJulian Evan-HartSpinksOffersUsed & Ex DemoGift Card Blog
